Guide to the George Wilson Pierson Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 1996-M-047
  - GWP's scrapbooks at Yale and from summer travel in Europe [preservation concerns], 1920s and 1930s (Box 8)
  - Correspondence [incoming], 1933-1936 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence [incoming], 1930s, 1950s (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, photographs, memorabilia of Eliza Day Pierson, dates to the, 1940s (Box 11)
  - Correspondence [incoming], 1920s - 1930s (Box 12)
  - Family papers (Box 12)
  - Estate papers (Box 12)
  - GWP's diaries and letters home from summer travel in Europe, late, 1920s - 1930s (Box 13)
  - GWP's student memorabilia, California letters, other letters, 1920s - 1952 (Box 14)
  - Family correspondence, 1940s - 1950s (Box 14)
  - Legal and financial files on property in Florida, NY and estate of Eliza D. Pierson, Circa 1952 (Box 14)
  - Photographs (Box 14)
  - Printed journals (Box 14)
  - Oversize correspondence, research material, and memorabilia, 1850-1976 (Box 15)
- Additional Material, Accession 1997-M-155
  - Personal, 1960s - 1980s (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous and genealogical, 1970s - 1980s (Box 2)
  - Clubs, 1960s - 1970s (Box 5)
  - Subject files (miscellaneous), 1960s - 1970s (Box 6)
  - Yale and personal, 1940s - 1990s (Box 7–9)
  - Writings [mostly lectures, speeches], 1950s - 1970s (Box 10–11)
  - Family Estates, 1950s - 1970s (Box 12)
  - George Pierson, writings [minister in Florida, Orange County, New York], 1820s - 1830s (Box 13–14)
- Additional Material, Accession 1999-M-084
  - Correspondence [outgoing]
    - Giamatti, Bart, 1978 August 12 (Box 1)
    - Noss, Luther, 1984 December 16 (Box 1)
  - "Yale Historical Statistics" [revised edition], 1972 (Box 1)